Finding Aid for University of Michigan Class Albums
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
University of Michigan Class Albums 1861-1887
[University of Michigan Class Albums]
9248 Bimu F99 2
The Class Albums collection consists of photograph albums compiled by University of Michigan students. The albums include individual and group portraits of class members, faculty portraits, and views of university buildings, the campus, and Ann Arbor scenes.
16 linear feet in 46 boxes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection has been brought together from the donations of many people. Some of the donor numbers are listed in the back of individual albums.
The collection is open for research.
Class albums of the late nineteenth century contain individual and group portraits of students and faculty as well as photos of university buildings, campus scenes, and some Ann Arbor street scenes. Beginning with the class of 1897, student portraits are found in the Michiganensian.
The albums themselves were compiled by students, hence the contents are determined by personal preferences of the students making the albums. Faculty photographs may often be identical with the portraits in the Faculty and Staff Portrait Collection, and are frequently duplicated between class albums as well.
The albums are arranged under series which are listed here chronologically by volume. Arrangement of photographs within volumes often begins with portraits faculty and administrators followed student portraits. Some volumes also include photos of campus buildings and other individuals. The portraits in each section are sometimes arranged alphabetically, but frequently there is no apparent order. Photos in most volumes have been given sequential identifying numbers. In the contents list below, the portraits are generally listed in alphabetical order with the identifying number in square brackets.
Summary Contents List
1861 (Literary) -- box 1
1861 (Literary) -- box 2
1861 (Medical) -- box 3
1862 (Law) -- box 3
1863 (Literary) -- box 4
1862 (Literary) -- box 4
1865 -- box 5
1867 -- box 6
1868 (Medical) -- box
1868 -- box 8
1868 -- box 9
1868 (Medical) -- box 10
1868 (Medical) -- box 10A
1869 -- box 11
1869 -- box 12
1870 -- box 13
1870 -- box 45 (copy 2)
1871 -- box 14
1871 -- box 15
1871 (Literary and Engineering) -- box 16
1872 -- box 17
1872 (3 copies, not identical) -- boxes-20
1872 (Literary and Engineering) (2 copies, not identical) -- boxes 21-22
1873 -- box 23
1873 (3 copies, not identical) -- boxes 24-26
1874 -- box 27
1874 -- box 28
1875 -- box29
1875 (Literary) -- box 30
1875 (partial) -- box 30A
1876 (Pharmacy) -- box 31
1876 -- box 32
1876 -- box 33
1876 -- box 34
1878 (Bound in 3 vols.) -- box 35-37
1878 -- box 38
1882 -- box 39
1882 -- box 40
1883 -- box 41
1885 -- box 42
1887 -- box 43
1875 -- box 44
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); University of Michigan--Buildings.; University of Michigan--Campus.; University of Michigan--Classes.; University of Michigan--Faculty.; University of Michigan--Students.
Genre Terms:
Albums.; Photographs.
- 1861 Class Album (Literary)
  (Photographed by T.D. Tooker, Ann Arbor)
  (Two volumes, not identical)
  - Buildings
    - North and South Halls, from south (Mason Hall) (Box 1)
      [1]
    - Medical Building (old) (Box 1)
      [2]
    - Detroit Observatory (Box 1)
      [3]
  - Faculty
    - Tappan, Henry Phillip 1805-1881 (Box 1)
      [4]
    - Williams, George Palmer 1802-1881 (Box 1)
      [5]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [6]
    - Douglas, Silas Hamilton 1816-1890 (Box 1)
      [7]
    - Fasquelle, Louis, 1808- (Box 1)
      [1962]
      [8]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [9]
    - Boise, Jas. R. [?] (Box 1)
      [10]
    - Palmer, Alonzo Benjamin 1815-1887 (Box 1)
      [11]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [12]
    - Evans, Edward Payson, 1831- (Box 1)
      [13]
    - Brunnow, Francis (Box 1)
      [14]
    - Ford, Corydon La 1813-1894 (Box 1)
      [15]
    - Frieze, H. [J?] Sn. (Box 1)
      [16]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [17]
    - Brooks, Davis C. (Box 1)
      [18]
    - White, A.O. (Box 1)
      [19]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [20]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [21]
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre 1824-1898 (Box 1)
      [22]
    - Wood, DeVolson 1832-1897 (Box 1)
      [23]
    - Watson, James Craig 1838-1880 (Box 1)
      [24]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [25]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [26]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [27]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [28]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [29]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [30]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [31]
    - "Jolly in Chapel" (Box 1)
      [32]
  - Students
    - Arn, Fred,-1862 (Box 1)
      [33]
    - Abbott, Orville Solomon,-1878 (Box 1)
      [34]
    - Adams, Charles Kendall,-1902 (Box 1)
      [35]
    - Aulls, Jas. Taylor,-1911 (Box 1)
      [36]
    - Beaver, Goodwin S., Albion, Mich.,-1865 (Box 1)
      [37]
    - Beadle, Wm. Henry Harrison,-1915 (Box 1)
      [38]
    - Dillings, Samuel Mead,-1901 (Box 1)
      [39]
    - Blair, B. Frank (Box 1)
      [40]
    - Cutcheon, Byron M.,-1908 (Box 1)
      [41]
    - Dedrick, Wm. Wirt,-1897 (Box 1)
      [42]
    - Denison, Charles Halbert,-1911 (Box 1)
      [43]
    - Dickinson, Edward (Box 1)
      [44]
    - Elliott, Isaac Hughes (Box 1)
      [45]
    - Flint, Homer Asaph,-1908 (Box 1)
      [46]
    - Gibson, Peter Silas,-1916 (Box 1)
      [47]
    - Gilette, Wm.,-1880 (Box 1)
      [48]
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
      [49]
    - Hall, Ephraim Gaylord (Box 1)
      [50]
    - Hagerman, James John (Box 1)
      [51]
    - Jackson, Edwd Seymour,-1910 (Box 1)
      [52]
    - Johnson, John Cyrus (Box 1)
      [53]
    - Johnston, [Ransford S.],-1906 (Box 1)
      [54]
    - Kelland, John,-1910 (Box 1)
      [55]
    - Landon, Henry Bishop (Box 1)
      [56]
    - Little, Eben Langdon (Box 1)
      [57]
    - Lord, John Smith,-1912 (Box 1)
      [58]
    - Lord, S.R.B. (Box 1)
      [59]
    - McAlister, Chas. Edson,-1901 (Box 1)
      [60]
    - Mc Collum, Walter,-1864 (Box 1)
      [61]
    - Mc Gowen, Jonas Hartzel,-1909 (Box 1)
      [62]
    - McWilliams, Samuel Anderson,-1917 (Box 1)
      [63]
    - Meserve, Charles Wesley,-1862 (Box 1)
      [64]
    - Morse, Sidney Goodman,-1862 (Box 1)
      [65]
    - Mills, Hiram Rollin,-1906 (Box 1)
      [66]
    - Nichols (Darwin) (Box 1)
      [67]
    - Newcomb, Henry Obadiah,-1870 (Box 1)
      [68]
    - Northrop, Stephen Johnson (Box 1)
      [69]
    - Perry, Walter Scott,-1897 (Box 1)
      [70]
    - Post, Hoyt, Detroit, Mich.,-1910 (Box 1)
      [71]
    - Post, James Alexis,-1913 (Box 1)
      [72]
    - Quick, Clavin Perin, Birmingham, Mich.,-1908 (Box 1)
      [73]
    - Sargent, Asa Carver,-1866 (Box 1)
      [74]
    - Sanford, George Poindexter,-1894 (Box 1)
      [75]
    - Searing, Edward,-1898 (Box 1)
      [76]
    - Stocking, Chas. Henry,-1881 (Box 1)
      [77]
    - Saunders, Wm. Henry,-1907 (Box 1)
      [78]
    - Taylor, [Rosweel Bayard,-1910] (Box 1)
      [80]
    - Utley, Henry Munson,-1917 (Box 1)
      [81]
    - Tripp, Robert Hall,-1917 (Box 1)
      [82]
    - Weir, Thomas Bell,-1876 (Box 1)
      [83]
    - Wood, Joseph Warren,-1914 (Box 1)
      [84]
    - Walker, Samuel Snow,-1909 (Box 1)
      [85]
  - 1861 Class Album (Box 2)
    (contains different pictures, in poor condition)
- 1861 Class Album (medical)
  - Faculty
    - Tappan, Henry P. (Box 3)
    - Palmer, Alonzo B. (Box 3)
    - Palmer, A.B. (Box 3)
    - Ford, Corydon La (Box 3)
    - Gunn, Minis (Box 3)
    - Sayer, Abraham (Box 3)
    - Douglass, Silas H. (Box 3)
    - Dubois, Alfred (Box 3)
    - Lewitt, William (Box 3)
    - Neryole (?), G. (Box 3)
  - Students
    - Alden, A.M. (Box 3)
    - Allen, A.L. (Box 3)
    - Bailey, William W. (Box 3)
    - Chase (Box 3)
    - Crawford (Box 3)
    - Curtis (Box 3)
    - Emerson, W.H. (Box 3)
    - Fraser (Box 3)
    - Hutchinson (Box 3)
    - Hutchinson (Box 3)
    - Koon (Box 3)
    - Momis, (?) (Box 3)
    - Phillips, Edwin (Box 3)
    - Smith, Willard B (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
      [14-20]
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
      [24-25]
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
      [34-37]
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
      [39-40]
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
      [42-45]
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
      [49-50]
    - Whitmore (Box 3)
    - Young (Box 3)
- 1862 Class Album (Law)
  (Mrs. O.B. Evans [Mae Chubb] was donor of book)
  - Faculty
    - Tappan, Henry Phillip (Box 3)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre (Box 3)
    - Campbell, James Valentine (Box 3)
  - Class
    - Andrus, William R. (Box 3)
    - Atkinson, John (Box 3)
    - Boylan, John Danes (Box 3)
    - Chubb, Joseph (Box 3)
    - Chubb, Mrs. Joseph and son (formerly Clarissa Lathrop) (Box 3)
    - Clark, Chas A. -- no picture (Box 3)
    - Compton, William Henry (Box 3)
    - Cowles, Albert Eugene (Box 3)
    - Denison, Thomas Riley (Box 3)
    - Dickson, Hiram Madison (Box 3)
    - Dilla, Wallace Delos (Box 3)
    - Douell, Donald M. -- No picture (Box 3)
    - Dutton, James B. (Box 3)
    - Earl, David Edward (Box 3)
    - Emerson, John Wesley (Box 3)
    - Evoy, A.M.M (Box 3)
    - Frisbie, Nelson L. (Box 3)
    - Gorrill, William H. (Box 3)
    - Haigler, William Franklin (Box 3)
    - Halls (?), Nelson B. -- no picture (Box 3)
    - Hawes, James Elliott (Box 3)
    - Hawes, Perry (Box 3)
    - Holden, Lewis S. (Box 3)
    - Johnson, J. Eastman (Box 3)
    - Kingsley, George (Box 3)
    - Kneeland, Samuel Miles (Box 3)
    - Lodge, Joseph G. (Box 3)
    - Macomber, Albert Everett (Box 3)
    - McEvoy, Andrew M. (Box 3)
    - Nelson, John Willis (Box 3)
    - Nichols, Henry Alonzo (Box 3)
    - Peirson, Levi Richards (Box 3)
    - Perkins, Daniel Webster (Box 3)
    - Pettibone, James Lyman (Box 3)
    - Porter, William Henry (Box 3)
    - Roberts, Morris (Box 3)
    - Shier, Daniel Ridgway (Box 3)
    - Slembrore (?) -- No picture (Box 3)
    - Smith, John S. (Box 3)
    - Taylor, Charles Henry (Box 3)
    - Thompson, Cyrus Josiah (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
    - Virden, Bethuel Addison (Box 3)
    - Walker, Ezra Carpenter (Box 3)
    - White, Henry Clay (Box 3)
    - Wiltsie, Wendell D. (Box 3)
    - Wixson, Levi L. (Box 3)
- 1862 Class Album (Literary)
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - Detroit Observatory (Box 4)
    - Nydia (Box 4)
    - Unidentified man near Medical Building (Box 4)
  - Faculty and Students
    - Tappan, Henry P., Chancellor (Box 4)
    - Allen, Alden (Box 4)
    - Ambruster, William E. (Box 4)
    - Anderson, Samuel R. (Box 4)
    - Baker, Rienzi Hiram (Box 4)
    - Baxter, Thomas Marshall (Box 4)
    - Beckington, Charles (Box 4)
    - Browne, Oliver L. (Box 4)
    - Burt, Hiram Austin (Box 4)
    - Carpenter, Roswell P. (Box 4)
    - Chandler, Charles, Jr. (Box 4)
    - Chapman, Albert J. (Box 4)
    - Cogshall, James Henry (Box 4)
    - Colby, John Ephraim (Box 4)
    - Critchett, Otis Adams (Box 4)
    - Crosby, Nathan (Box 4)
    - D'Ooge, Martin Luther (Box 4)
    - Eastman, James Edwin (Box 4)
    - Edward Allen Fay (Box 4)
    - Follett, Harmon Dewey (Box 4)
    - Howard, Samuel (Box 4)
    - Hurd, Charles (Box 4)
    - Hurd, Theodore Hammond (Box 4)
    - Jewett, Aaron Cone (Box 4)
    - Joseph C. Greenawalt (Box 4)
    - Latson, Henry Arthur (Box 4)
    - Lewis, Charles Henry (Box 4)
    - Lovejoy, David Harmon (Box 4)
    - Marr, George Anson (Box 4)
    - Nelson, William Eugene (Box 4)
    - Newman, Jonathan W. (Box 4)
    - Nye, Albert (Box 4)
    - Pilcher, Lewis S. F. (Box 4)
    - Richards, William V. (Box 4)
    - Rosebrugh, Moses Kelly (Box 4)
    - Samuel Erastus Perry (Box 4)
    - Sloan, Henry H. (Box 4)
    - Uhl, Edwin Fuller (Box 4)
    - Unidentified man (Box 4)
    - Van Keuren, James Irvin (Box 4)
    - Watkins, Aaron A. (Box 4)
    - Wells, Elmore H. (Box 4)
    - Wheeler, Charles H. (Box 4)
    - Wheeler, Orlando B. (Box 4)
    - Wood, Charles Beers (Box 4)
- 1865 Class Album
  - Faculty
    - Boise, James Robinson (Box 5)
    - Chapin, Lucius Delison (Box 5)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre (Box 5)
    - Douglas, Silas Hamilton (Box 5)
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons (Box 5)
    - Palmer, Alonzo Benjamin (Box 5)
    - Spence, Adam Knight (Box 5)
    - Tappan, Henry Phillip (Box 5)
    - Williams, George Palmer (Box 5)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 5)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 5)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 5)
    - Ex-Principal of Ypsilanti Union (Box 5)
    - Seminary and Principal of Normal School (Box 5)
    - Estabrook (Box 5)
    - Sculptor with honorary degree (Box 5)
    - Rogers, Randolph (Box 5)
  - Campus Buildings
    - The Detroit Observatory of the U. of M. (Box 5)
    - Statue--Nydia (Box 5)
  - Class
    - Unthank, Achilles W. (Box 5)
    - Walker, Francis Laruna (Box 5)
    - Williams, Charles Gilmore (Box 5)
    - Wisner, George Young (Box 5)
    - Lovejoy, David Harmon (Box 5)
    - Barstow, Carlton Edward (Box 5)
    - Aldrich, Abram J. (Box 5)
    - Barnes, William H. (Box 5)
    - Bills, Oscar P. (Box 5)
    - Bond, Pleasant (Box 5)
    - Bouton, William (Box 5)
    - Campbell, Gabriel (Box 5)
    - Clark, Stephen W. (Box 5)
    - Cornelius, James D.H. (Box 5)
    - Curtis, Orson B. (Box 5)
    - Dudley, Charles A. (Box 5)
    - Fifield, William H. (Box 5)
    - Goodrich, Eward P. (Box 5)
    - Goodsell, Charles M. (Box 5)
    - Hill, Arthur (Box 5)
    - Jennings, Albert (Box 5)
    - Keller, David (Box 5)
    - Ladd, Sanford (Box 5)
    - Maynard, William J. (Box 5)
    - McKenzie, David (Box 5)
    - McKercher, James C. (Box 5)
    - Monroe, Daniel (Box 5)
    - Nixon, James P. (Box 5)
    - Phillips, Delos (Box 5)
    - Powers, Homer C. (Box 5)
    - Root, John Barnes (Box 5)
    - Sanford, Charles Addison (Box 5)
    - Snow, Arthur Herbert (Box 5)
    - Thompson, John (Box 5)
- 1867 Class Album
  - Album of David B. Taylor (Box 6)
    (The vast majority of photographs are unidentified on the pages, however, some May be identified on their backsides. Their removal from the pages of the album is often difficult.)
- 1868 Class Album (Medical)
  - President of the United States
    - Abraham Lincoln (Box 7)
  - Faculty
    - Group picture of class members (Box 7)
    - Group pictures (6) of the faculty (Box 7)
      (including: Rev. Erastas Otis Haven, Moses Gunn, Corydon La Ford, Samuel Glasgow Armor, Abram Sager, and others)
    - Armor, Samuel Glasgow (2) (Box 7)
    - Douglass, Silas H. (Box 7)
    - Ford, Corydon La (2) (Box 7)
    - Greene, William Warren (Box 7)
    - Gunn, Moses (2) (Box 7)
    - Haven, Rev. Erastus Otis (2) (Box 7)
    - Prescott, Albert Benjamin (Box 7)
    - Sager, Abram (2) (Box 7)
    - Berrell, Dwight R. (Box 7)
    - Cooper, Aaron W. (Box 7)
    - Dodsley, Henry (Box 7)
    - Downing, W. Lee (Box 7)
    - Elliot, Thos. Thomas (Box 7)
    - Fearon, Robert N. (Box 7)
    - Kendrick, Jos. (Box 7)
    - Farrington, Stephen S. (Box 7)
    - Moore, George Oramel (Box 7)
    - Revenaugh, Aurelius 0. (Box 7)
    - Sturdevant, John Emory (Box 7)
    - Sackett, E. K. (Box 7)
    - Wilder, Flavius Myron (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Dentistry (humorous picture) (Box 7)
    - Intestines (Box 7)
- 1868 Class Album
  (Album of W.R. Anderson)
  - Faculty, Students and Miscellaneous
    - Moses Coit Tyler (Box 8)
    - Geo. P. Williams (Box 8)
    - Univ. of Mich. (Box 8)
    - Univ. of Mich. (Box 8)
    - Jas. T. Bois (Box 8)
    - E.O. Haven (Box 8)
    - Surveying class (Box 8)
    - Henry S. Frieze (Box 8)
    - A. Winchell (Box 8)
    - E.P. Evans (Box 8)
    - Danl G. Cash '67 (Box 8)
    - Wm. Hitt. Readle a. 61, '67, hon. (Box 8)
    - A.B. Palmer (Box 8)
    - A. Ten Brook (Box 8)
    - 3 girls (Box 8)
    - Wickliffe W. Belville a. 68 (Box 8)
    - E. Olney (Box 8)
    - Deldson Wood/W.A. Underwood (left) (Box 8)
    - (Joel?) Kelsey (Box 8)
    - woman (Box 8)
    - Jas. C. Watson (Box 8)
    - S. H. Douglass (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Bracy (Box 8)
    - bas relief (Box 8)
    - W.W. Belville a. 68 (Box 8)
    - (illegible) (Box 8)
    - Thomas Speed /65-66 (Box 8)
    - F.M. Bain e 68 (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Little Pilgrim/unidentified (left) (Box 8)
    - W.A. Underwood (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Edw. C. Burns e.68 (Box 8)
    - 3 girls (Box 8)
    - University Hall (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - unidentified man + woman (Box 8)
    - 2 men (Box 8)
    - B.R. Chaffee, e.'68 (Box 8)
    - Brutus J. Clay, e. 68, hon.'78 (Box 8)
    - woman (Box 8)
    - Will H. Anderson (woman) (Box 8)
    - man-unidentified (Box 8)
    - J. B. Davis, e.'68, hon. 78 (Box 8)
    - Mrs. Martha C. Hing (Box 8)
    - man, unidentified (Box 8)
    - J.J. Davis a.68 (Box 8)
    - man, unidentified (Box 8)
    - group of men, The Owls? (Box 8)
    - W.A. Underwood & ? (2 boys) (Box 8)
    - T.N. Denimon '68 (Box 8)
    - Henry R. Durkee a'68 (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Cornelius A. Gower a'67 (Box 8)
    - Torbert Entrerin e'68 (Box 8)
    - John Chas. Freeman (Box 8)
    - W.A. Underwood (Box 8)
    - Benj. F. Stage /'66 (Box 8)
    - Geo Cook Fry (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Loulou's hand (Box 8)
    - unidentified woman (Box 8)
    - Mark Walrod Harrington (Box 8)
    - Milo K. Havens (Box 8)
    - Sue E. Bradford (Box 8)
    - David Rodman Murray (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Geo. Smith Hickey (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Richard B. Robinson a'64-'66/Isaac W. Heysinger (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Edw. S. Jenison (Box 8)
    - Lewis S. Pilcher (Box 8)
    - R.B. Robinson '68 (Box 8)
    - Roselle N. Jenne (Box 8)
    - Henry S. Jewett (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [79]
    - Lloyd B. Selby a'66-'67 (Box 8)
    - Edgar S. Johnston e'68 m'79 (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
    - Geo. Adelbert Foster a'67 (Box 8)
    - Allie Harnicle (?) (Box 8)
    - Henry W. Lord a'68 (Box 8)
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [86]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [87]
    - Dog & puppies in a flood (Box 8)
      [88]
    - F.H. Lyman a'68 (Box 8)
      [89]
    - John C. Magill (Box 8)
      [90]
    - Arthur A. Abbott (Box 8)
      [91]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [92]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [93]
    - Humphrey H. C. Miller a'68 (Box 8)
      [94]
    - Percy R. Sawyer (Box 8)
      [95]
    - Arnold Sawyer (Box 8)
      [96]
    - A. H. Pattengill (Box 8)
      [97]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [98]
    - Louis P. Judson e'67/John O. Andrews a'67 (Box 8)
      [99]
    - Philetus H. Philbrick a68 e68 (Box 8)
      [101]
    - Chas. Poor (Box 8)
      [102]
    - 103.-unidentified (Box 8)
      [104]
    - Lorenzo B. Potts a'68 (Box 8)
      [105]
    - Thomas C. Raynolds a'68 (Box 8)
      [106]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [107-109]
    - Fillmore M. Smith e'68 (Box 8)
      [110]
    - John Graham Brooks /'67-'68 (Box 8)
      [111]
    - E.S. Jenison (Box 8)
      [112]
    - Wm. J. Cocker a'69 (Box 8)
      [113]
    - Riley Clark Story a'68 (Box 8)
      [114]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [115-116]
    - Joseph M. Stoutt a'68 (Box 8)
      [117]
    - Wm. J. Stuart (Box 8)
      [118]
    - U. of M. Museum Statuary (Box 8)
      [119]
      [120]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [121]
    - Llew. P. Tarlton a.68 (Box 8)
      [122]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [123-124]
    - Edward L. Walter a.68 (Box 8)
      [125]
    - Milford N. Wells e.68 (Box 8)
      [126]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [127]
    - Frank Carleton/W.S. Robison (Box 8)
      [128]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [129]
    - H.W. Stevenson l.69 (Box 8)
      [130]
    - 4 men-Hathaway (?), Helm (?) (Box 8)
      [132]
    - Ida Bille Winchill/Katie Wilsey (Box 8)
      [133]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [138]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [142-146]
    - Martha Washington (portrait) (Box 8)
      [147]
    - George Washington (portrait) (Box 8)
      [148]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [149]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [153]
    - Randall (?) (Box 8)
      [154]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [155]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [157]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [159]
    - Emma Anderson (Box 8)
      [160]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [161-162]
    - S.S. Avery a.67-68 (Box 8)
      [163]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [164]
    - D. Bruce McEwen (Box 8)
      [165]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [167-172]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [175-176]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [179-180]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [183]
    - A. J. Reeves l.61 (Box 8)
      [184]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [186]
    - Mary Reeves (Box 8)
      [187]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [188-191]
    - C.M. Winchell e.73 (Box 8)
      [192]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [193-194]
    - Jennie C. Winchell (Box 8)
      [195]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [196]
    - John G. Weir (Box 8)
      [197]
    - Charlie M. MacLaren (Box 8)
      [198]
    - unidentified (Box 8)
      [199]
    - "Sid" Group (unidentified) (Box 8)
      [200]
- 1868 Class Album
  (Album of Demmon, J.N.)
  - Faculty
    - Angell, James B. (Box 9)
    - Williams, George P. (Box 9)
    - Douglass, Silas H. (Box 9)
    - Boise, James (Box 9)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 9)
    - Frieze, Henry S. (Box 9)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 9)
    - Evans, E. P. (Box 9)
    - Chapin, Lucius D. (Box 9)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 9)
    - Palmer, Alonzo B. (Box 9)
    - Spence, Adam K. (Box 9)
    - Adams, Charles K. (Box 9)
    - Curtis, Allen J. (Box 9)
    - Prescott, Albert B. (Box 9)
    - Robinson, Stillman W. (Box 9)
    - Tappan, Henry P. (Box 9)
    - Ten Brook, Andrew (Box 9)
    - Haven, Erstus O. (Box 9)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 9)
    - D'Ooge, Martin, L. (Box 9)
    - several unidentified photos (Box 9)
  - Students
    - Anderson, W.K. (Box 9)
    - Bain, P.M. (Box 9)
    - Belville, W.W. (Box 9)
    - Blackburn, F.A. (Box 9)
    - Boardman, W.H. (Box 9)
    - Burns, E.C. (Box 9)
    - Carter, A. (Box 9)
    - Chafee, B.R. (Box 9)
    - Chapin, J.H. (Box 9)
    - Clay, B.J. (Box 9)
    - Crouse, D.W. (Box 9)
    - Davis, J.B. (Box 9)
    - Davis, J.J. (Box 9)
    - Dean, O.H. (Box 9)
    - Demmon, I.N. (Box 9)
    - Durkee, H.R. (Box 9)
    - Entrekin, T. (Box 9)
    - Freeman, J.C. (Box 9)
    - Fry, G.C (Box 9)
    - Gale, E.W. (Box 9)
    - Harrington, M.W. (Box 9)
    - Havens, M.K. (Box 9)
    - Hessenmueller, E.L. (Box 9)
    - Kickey, G.S. (Box 9)
    - Howell, C.N. (Box 9)
    - Jenison, E.S. (Box 9)
    - Jenne, R.N. (Box 9)
    - Jewett, H.S. (Box 9)
    - Johnston, Edgar S. (Box 9)
    - Kingsley, W.A. (Box 9)
    - Lord, H.W. (Box 9)
    - Lovell, E. C. (Box 9)
    - Lyman, F.H. (Box 9)
    - Magill, J.C. (Box 9)
    - McHarg(?), W.S. (Box 9)
    - Miller, H.H. (Box 9)
    - Pattengill, A.H. (Box 9)
    - Pennell, G. (Box 9)
    - Philbrick, C.E. (Box 9)
    - Poor, C. (Box 9)
    - Potts, L.B. (Box 9)
    - Reeves, R. J. (Box 9)
    - Smith, F.M. (Box 9)
    - Steere, J.B. (Box 9)
    - Storey, R.C. (Box 9)
    - Stoutt (Box 9)
    - Stuart, W.J. (Box 9)
    - Tallman, E.H. (Box 9)
    - Tarlton, L.P. (Box 9)
    - Walter, E.L. (Box 9)
    - Wells, M.N. (Box 9)
    - Coffey, J.C. '70 (Box 9)
    - House, J.H. '68 (Box 9)
    - Kendall, J.L. '68 (Box 9)
    - Buttler, W. '69 (Box 9)
    - Mack, A.J. '68 (Box 9)
    - Morrill, F.F. '68 (Box 9)
    - Mank, A.J. '64 (Box 9)
    - Perkings, W.R. '64 (Box 9)
    - Wilson, A. '64 (Box 9)
    - Brainard, F.A. '64 (Box 9)
    - Shaw, T.M. '68 (Box 9)
    - Crocker, W.J. '68, '69 (Box 9)
    - Dewey, R.S. '68 (Box 9)
    - Beazell, J.S. '67 (Box 9)
    - Whiffen, J.W. '67 (Box 9)